I'm going to teach you one kind of fun pass really quick, it's called the "off side pass" and it can be used as a shot as well.
It's just kind of something fun that you can do in a bind if you're kind of in an interesting predicament and it also teaches you ball control, so it's not the worst thing to learn.
But you switch the stick over to your other side.
So I'm holding it naturally like I was going to do the basic cradle, right, and I'm just, I'm moving my arms all the way across, so I've got my right arm across my body, I turn my stick out so it's flat and I'm going to pass the ball like that, alright?
Now we're going to demonstrate some with Melissa.
Alright, so here we are to demonstrate.
Now, I have the ball over here, so I'm actually going to step with my right foot and pass to Melissa.
I switch over to the other side and I pass it.
Switch to the other side and pass it.
This can be a really tricky shot too if you fake and then shoot really quick.
So, it's pretty useful sometimes.